## JENNIE GONG

022 328 1286 xinning.gong@gmail.com https://jenniegong.vercel.app/

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I am a hard-working, curious and self-motivated person with a passion for IT. I love analysing data and problem solving as I find connecting information and forming relationships fascinating. I have studied a myriad of coding languages for 6 years and have completed many personal and academic projects. I am adaptable and a quick learner. For example, I learnt to create a google chrome extension and use typescript at a hackathon within 2 hours. I am able to work effectively independently and with a team.

#### **SKILLS AND STRENGTHS**

- JavaScript created a hangman app, use jQuery 3.3.1 to create webpage
- R Use R Markdown to model and analyse data, ggplot2 to produce graphs, tidyverse, web scraping, data wrangling
- Database MySQL, PHP, DB
   Browser, Amazon cloud services,
   Microsoft SQL server
- **Python** learnt for 6 years
- Java learnt for 1 year
- Excel solve linear programming problems, pivot tables, data entry and analytics
- Front end web dev- multiple page dynamic, responsive website with database
- Design experience with photoshop, canva, Adobe XD and powerpoint
- Websphere process modelling
- ER Modelling, project proposal, data modelling, normalisation, json, XML
- Excellent analytical and problem-solving skills

#### PROJECTS AND EXPERIENCE

## **Reddit Webapp and Chrome Extension**

WDCC x SESA Hackathon | 2021

- Built webapp that looks like VS code using reddit API and displayed posts as code for the theme of procrastination
- Created google chrome extension to allow easy access to webapp using json and javascript
- Created presentation and promotional video
- Received best design award for demonstrating excellence in UI/UX design

# **Webportal** with project proposal and deliverable UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND GROUP PROJECT | 2020

- Develop a business proposal to create web portal for a career agency with use case models, functions outline, prototype documentation, test plan and design principles.
- Use AdobeXD to create multiple GUI prototypes for different device types.
- Presentation of project to stakeholders and project manager.
- Received A grade for overall project.

## **AgTech Hackathon 2019**

ZESPRI | 2019

- Work in a team to develop a solution to optimise kiwifruit production in 40 hours.
- Design a prototype using Adobe XD of web app.
- Create web app using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery.
- Use Photoshop to design media for app.
- Placed second overall in competition and received internship from Zespri to continue idea.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Auckland**

MAR 2020 - PRESENT

Bachelor of Science, majoring in Statistics and Information Technology Management (Expected graduation Nov 2022)

## **Massey University**

FEB 2019 - NOV 2019

Certificate of Proficiency Undergraduate

## Palmerston North Girls High School

JAN 2015 - NOV 2019

2019 - Year 13, achieved NCEA level 3 with excellence endorsement: 60 Excellence credits and 28 Merit credits

#### OTHER EXPERIENCE

- Mentee at Cisco MentorMe
   2021 Programme
- Alpha Tester for Fist Bump a startup aimed to connect students using an algorithm
- Summer internship teaching English in Nanjing, China 2019-2020
- Waitress at Goan Korean BBQ Restaurant and Hana Mizu Ki Restaurant 2018-2019

# EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- UoA Class Rep
- UoA Information System and Business Analytics Society
- UoA Web Development & Consulting Club
- UoA Developers Society
- UoA Google Developer Student Club
- Beta Alpha Sci
- Auckland Student Pool Association
- UoA Kiwi Asian Club
- Auckland University Chinese Student Society
- UoA Kpop Planet
- VEX Robotics
- NZ UN Youth
- Youth Judge at the Manawatu Science Fair
- PNGHS academic tutor

#### **WEBSITES**

#### Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/jenniegong

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/xinninggong

#### REFEREES

#### **David Smith**

Professional Teaching Fellow University of Auckland

#### Lucy Eberhardt

Marketing Manager The Plaza Shopping Centre

Out of courtesy to my referees, details are available on request.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Teaching Assistant**

#### UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND | MAR 2021 - PRESENT

- Mark assessments and record data entry associated with marks in appropriate university systems
- Summarise common student errors and areas of improvement for individual students

#### Sales and Services Assistant

FARMERS PALMERSTON NORTH | 2020 - 2021

- Processed sales, exchanges, customer orders and stock transfers using POS system
- Troubleshoot and assist the security and sales team with technical issues
- Assist customers with queries and purchasing decisions

#### **Promotions Assistant**

#### THE PLAZA SHOPPING CENTRE | 2017 - 2019

- Assist in promoting and marketing events
- Handling customers and general enquiries
- Opening, cleaning and closing down booths
- Running activities and supervising children

#### **AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### 2021

• WDCC x SESA Hackathon Best Design Award

#### 2020

 UoA Certificate of Outstanding Achievement in Computer Science

#### Certificate of Achievement for Commitment and Leadership as UoA Class Representative

 UoA Certificate of Distinction in Statistics

#### Prior to 2020

- Placed second at AgTech Hackathon with web app to optimise kiwifruit production
- Attended NanoCamp in Canterbury University for top NZ science students
- Langley Memorial Prize Manawatu Science Fair
- Fonterra High Distinction at Manawatu Science Fair
- Bronze CREST
- High school Prefect Award
- High Distinction in NCSS challenge Intermediate category

- UOA Academic Potential Scholarship
- Course Distinction Award NCEA Level 3 English, Statistics and Accounting with first place in Statistics and Accounting
- PNGHS Gifted and Talented programme
- Elite Award for Education
   Perfect Maths placing in the top
   100 globally
- Laureate for Music achieving Grade 8 piano with merit
- Bronze Award Chamber Music placing in the top 30 nationally